<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Bomby&#39;s Website!</title>
    <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Bomby&#39;s Website!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/front-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/front-matter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quick update today since I got carried away by this website again (it always happen out of nowhere I swear!), but it&amp;rsquo;s already 1:22am where I am! (Ohno&amp;hellip; and I&amp;rsquo;ve got work tomorrow morning)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying out something new (again)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This something new is Front Matter – a CMS extension for VS Code that lets me write my markdown for my blogposts using WYSIWYG (What You See is What You Get).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s been a hot minute... (2 years almost!)</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/hot-minute-2-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:55:23 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/hot-minute-2-years/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh wow, it&amp;rsquo;s been almost two years since I last updated this site&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So so so much have happened in these last two years. I got a job working as a Junior UI/UX designer at an awesome place and learnt more about code as well!
There are so many things I could do better with this site structurally&amp;hellip;
I still love it though! This is the first web project that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed myself. :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll try to build another site though! With skills I learnt on the job maybe hehe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh long story short, I&amp;rsquo;ll finally be able to go on my exchange to Japan next month!
I&amp;rsquo;ll be at Niigata for 11 months, so that&amp;rsquo;s pretty big. :O&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This means that my bf and I will have to do long distance until I come back&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wow, it&#39;s like I&#39;m in another dimension!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 22:21:38 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey there! Guess I&amp;rsquo;m pretty bad at keeping up a digital journal.&lt;br&gt;
It&amp;rsquo;s already been 2 weeks since I last posted!&lt;br&gt;
COVID&amp;rsquo;s starting to get bad again where I live, so the snow trip that I&amp;rsquo;m super looking forward to might get cancelled. 😭&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently got an Oculus Quest II mainly for my dad to try out. He&amp;rsquo;s always been a huge fan of tech and video games. VR headsets must&amp;rsquo;ve been like a sci-fi object back in his days. At the moment, we both enjoy games that are a bit more chill, without the need to move around too much. (Mostly because we&amp;rsquo;re both prone to motion sickness)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of the Oculus summer sales, I bought Vacation simulator! I also tried out the 3D painting app Quill on PCVR. And of course, Beat Saber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VR is so cool!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My holidays have been a little unproductive so far, but I&amp;rsquo;ll crank it up tomorrow. We finally got our club confirmed! I&amp;rsquo;ll also try to continue my exercises on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freecodecamp.org&#34;&gt;freeCodeCamp&lt;/a&gt;. I should be able to finish the Responsive Web Design Certification course very soon. Currently debating with myself whether I should skip the JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification course and go straight into Front End Development Libraries since I&amp;rsquo;ve already worked with Java at uni.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I should maybe also make a new blog that&amp;rsquo;s a little more professional for my own portfolio&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you think?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter break</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 19:10:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Haven&amp;rsquo;t posted for almost a while, but I&amp;rsquo;m done with uni for the semester!&lt;br&gt;
I coded a website showcasing my poster and zine design for an assignment.&lt;br&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This holidays, I want to get better at coding and design some materials for my Café Club. I&amp;rsquo;m excited for it to get up and running!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holidays... SOON!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 18:59:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t poster in a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with uni assignments. My last one is due on the 31st of this month, so not too long to go!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University has been fun for the first semester, but I definitely can use a break over the winter holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this holiday, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on a website for a society that I&amp;rsquo;m starting, as well as trying to learn more coding. TwilioQuest seems like a fun way to do that and I might try it in combination with FreeCodeCamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll also be going to the snow this year, so here&amp;rsquo;s to hoping that we get some nice and fluffy show when we&amp;rsquo;re there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catmap 2</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 18:30:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-07/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy the last few days working on the catmap, and I got the Google Maps API to work the way I want it to!
So far, I have 40 pictures, but I still need 60 more for the assignment criteria.
It was interesting to look at the different interpretations of cats around the world, and the myths and stories that follow&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ll finish up with those on the weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INFP</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 17:39:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just worked today, nothing much else!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Myers-briggs personality test (and many other like it) isn&amp;rsquo;t based on any real scientific research, but something about personality tests really intrigue me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s the idea that we can truly understand people and all the complexities and differences that make these tests so compelling. It&amp;rsquo;s plain satisfying to feel that everyone&amp;rsquo;s differences has an underlying reason&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But no!! People are more than just 4 letters. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit of fun, but I think most people&amp;rsquo;s personalities are fluid and change depending on the environment they&amp;rsquo;re in and the people they&amp;rsquo;re with.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catmap</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 20:06:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I tried to do something cool for my upcoming assignment with code.&lt;br&gt;
Unfortunately, being the big noob I am, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really figure it out.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted to create a map with pictures overlaid on certain coordinates, and tried to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://openlayers.org/&#34;&gt;OpenLayers&lt;/a&gt; to do it.&lt;br&gt;
For most of the day, I was figuring out how to use npm and browserify to run packages&amp;hellip;  I&amp;rsquo;m happy that I learnt how to use them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the map, I actually did manage to embed it onto the page, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand how to project a static image onto specific coordinates.&lt;br&gt;
You can take a look &lt;a href=&#34;http://bomby.neocities.org/projects/catmap/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!
Not exciting at all since it&amp;rsquo;s just a map, but it&amp;rsquo;s better than nothing. 😭&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I might try to use Google Maps API instead just because the documentation is easier to read (for me).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:00:30 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I swear 9am lectures are my worst enemies&amp;hellip; Especially when the next class is at 1:30pm!! They should&amp;rsquo;ve just kept the lecture before class&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s not the worst thing in the world though, since I usually go to a cafe with my friends in the down-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;



&lt;a href=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/65xf5pVD/AC4-FC0-CD-C035-4-F18-A5-C4-5468-ED0-A5-CE0.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/65xf5pVD/AC4-FC0-CD-C035-4-F18-A5-C4-5468-ED0-A5-CE0.jpg&#34; style=&#34;max-height: 300px&#34; alt=&#34;Photo of my lecture&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Learning about street posters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sitting at the back is fun because I can see what everyone else is distracted by&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posting from mobile...?</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 07:26:57 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-29/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just downloaded the app &lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.apple.com/au/app/working-copy-git-client/id896694807&#34;&gt;Working Copy&lt;/a&gt; on my iPhone so that I can clone my git repository and create markdown files on the go!  I also got the app &lt;a href=&#34;https://apps.apple.com/au/app/bear/id1016366447&#34;&gt;Bear&lt;/a&gt; for nicer mark-down editing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;



&lt;a href=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/BQc3Phfj/E0357-CCD-0-A97-41-E2-A1-F5-50-FB32-F3-EE8-B.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/BQc3Phfj/E0357-CCD-0-A97-41-E2-A1-F5-50-FB32-F3-EE8-B.jpg&#34; style=&#34;max-height: 500px&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot of the Working Copy app&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Working copy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woohoo!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 15:39:42 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m so happy!!!&lt;br&gt;
I finally figured out how to get VSCode to build and push new changes of my Hugo website to Neocities automatically.&lt;br&gt;
This problem took me so long to solve (with a lot of experimentation) because all the tools I found were far too technical for a n00b like me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ll give you in a nutshell of how I did it! (Special thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://neocities.org/site/kirbykevinson&#34;&gt;Kirby Kevinson&lt;/a&gt; on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.com/invite/eSBb68a&#34;&gt;Penny&amp;rsquo;s Club discord&lt;/a&gt; server for giving me the hint of using GitLab.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;a href=&#34;https://about.gitlab.com/images/press/logo/jpg/gitlab-logo-gray-rgb.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://about.gitlab.com/images/press/logo/jpg/gitlab-logo-gray-rgb.jpg&#34; style=&#34;max-height:200px&#34; alt=&#34;Gitlab Logo&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just a work and uni kinda day...</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:23:32 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-27/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that I have a system (kinda) working with Hugo and Neocities, I can focus on just writing my blog! Yay. Today, I just went to work and had classes between my shifts. To be honest, the whole day, I was just thinking about how I can get my website to automatically push itself to Neocities&amp;hellip; 😆&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I might&amp;rsquo;ve figured it out by using the Github actions: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/marketplace/actions/deploy-to-neocities&#34;&gt;Deploy to Neocities&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;ll update to let you know if it actually works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Class today was fun&amp;hellip; We just played around with inks and the like. Messy, but fun.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;a href=&#34;https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ecccf5b8-89c1-4c14-b3cd-cd3d2343c849&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/ecccf5b8-89c1-4c14-b3cd-cd3d2343c849&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Animated gif of Kirby with sparkly eyes&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Post!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 23:14:57 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-26/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t published the website yet since I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to figure out how to get the date and images showing properly for the blog&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;a href=&#34;https://64.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lp89s4uVFM1qiog0do1_400.gif&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://64.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lp89s4uVFM1qiog0do1_400.gif&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Animated gif of Kirby crying&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Edit: I&amp;rsquo;ve figured out how to do the dates properly! Turns out all my blog posts had to follow the YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ss+15:00 (+15:00 is my timezone ahead of CST) in order for Hugo to render it properly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 23:14:57 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-25/</guid>
      <description>I just migrated my static website to Hugo! This will make it easier for me to do blog posts. :D</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
