<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uni on Bomby&#39;s Website!</title>
    <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/tags/uni/</link>
    <description>Recent content in uni on Bomby&#39;s Website!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 19:10:13 +1500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bomby.neocities.org/tags/uni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Winter break</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 19:10:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-06-03/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Haven&amp;rsquo;t posted for almost a while, but I&amp;rsquo;m done with uni for the semester!&lt;br&gt;
I coded a website showcasing my poster and zine design for an assignment.&lt;br&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;d say I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with the result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This holidays, I want to get better at coding and design some materials for my Café Club. I&amp;rsquo;m excited for it to get up and running!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holidays... SOON!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 18:59:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t poster in a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy with uni assignments. My last one is due on the 31st of this month, so not too long to go!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;University has been fun for the first semester, but I definitely can use a break over the winter holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During this holiday, I&amp;rsquo;ll be working on a website for a society that I&amp;rsquo;m starting, as well as trying to learn more coding. TwilioQuest seems like a fun way to do that and I might try it in combination with FreeCodeCamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll also be going to the snow this year, so here&amp;rsquo;s to hoping that we get some nice and fluffy show when we&amp;rsquo;re there.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catmap 2</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-07/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 18:30:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-07/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy the last few days working on the catmap, and I got the Google Maps API to work the way I want it to!
So far, I have 40 pictures, but I still need 60 more for the assignment criteria.
It was interesting to look at the different interpretations of cats around the world, and the myths and stories that follow&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;ll finish up with those on the weekend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catmap</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 20:06:13 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-05-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, I tried to do something cool for my upcoming assignment with code.&lt;br&gt;
Unfortunately, being the big noob I am, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t really figure it out.&lt;br&gt;
I wanted to create a map with pictures overlaid on certain coordinates, and tried to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://openlayers.org/&#34;&gt;OpenLayers&lt;/a&gt; to do it.&lt;br&gt;
For most of the day, I was figuring out how to use npm and browserify to run packages&amp;hellip;  I&amp;rsquo;m happy that I learnt how to use them!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the map, I actually did manage to embed it onto the page, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand how to project a static image onto specific coordinates.&lt;br&gt;
You can take a look &lt;a href=&#34;http://bomby.neocities.org/projects/catmap/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!
Not exciting at all since it&amp;rsquo;s just a map, but it&amp;rsquo;s better than nothing. 😭&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I might try to use Google Maps API instead just because the documentation is easier to read (for me).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class!</title>
      <link>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:00:30 +1500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bomby.neocities.org/blog/2021-04-30/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I swear 9am lectures are my worst enemies&amp;hellip; Especially when the next class is at 1:30pm!! They should&amp;rsquo;ve just kept the lecture before class&amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s not the worst thing in the world though, since I usually go to a cafe with my friends in the down-time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;



&lt;a href=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/65xf5pVD/AC4-FC0-CD-C035-4-F18-A5-C4-5468-ED0-A5-CE0.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;blogimage&#34; src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/65xf5pVD/AC4-FC0-CD-C035-4-F18-A5-C4-5468-ED0-A5-CE0.jpg&#34; style=&#34;max-height: 300px&#34; alt=&#34;Photo of my lecture&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Learning about street posters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sitting at the back is fun because I can see what everyone else is distracted by&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
